

Marc Kevin Flores

WEB DEVELOPER / CROSS-PLATFORM MOBILE DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Energetic and motivated developer with 5 years of experience in building a website and mobile application, including designing a user interface, testing, debugging, optimizing interactive, and maintaining function. A clear understanding of modern technologies and best practices. Ability to learn and collaborate in rapidly changing environments and compositions

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address

BLK 2 LOT 10 Cameron St. Princetown Subd. Bagumbong Caloocan City, Metro Manila, Philippines (click to google map)

CONTACT

- - marc@kevinflor.es
- +639092884082
- https://kevinflor.es
- in marckevinflores
- marckevinflores

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

MICROSOURCING

Aug 2023 - Present

- Create wireframes using Figma for both desktop and mobile design then write them into to website template.
- Convert the web design mockup to a microsite template using web frameworks.
- Worked with 4 developers and 5 product managers to create a promotion website with different
- Fixed front-end issues related to design perfection and responsive layouts.
- Worked with international teams on the AEST Timezone.

Tech Stacks: JavaScript, PHP, Figma, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap 5

Software Engineer

YONDU INC.

Sep 2022 - Aug 2023 (1 yrs)

- Developed on-demand booking features and modules while managing state using redux for a booking delivery app
- Developed code standards and reusable UI components to be easily implemented and understood by other teams.
- Worked in an agile software development team to complete various epics through sprints.
- Worked with international teams such as project managers, scrum masters, developers, and quality assurance to resolve technical issues.

Tech Stacks: JavaScript, React.js, React Native, Typescript

Software Developer

DIGITAL DOORS SOFTWARE SOLUTIONS INC

Jul 2019 - Sep 2022 (3 yrs 3 mos)

- Maintain and update e-commerce website for new features.
- Developed backend API, Mobile Web (SPA), Android, and IOS applications.
- Published Web and mobile apps to the Play Store, App Store, and Web Hosting for new updates and bug fixes.
- Integrated third-party API and services for payment, logistics, analytics, and cloud messaging.
- Collaborated with product management, marketing, and designers.
- Created reusable code to reduce bundle size and improve performance.
- Developed custom state management to work on multiple pages.
- Run, build and debug a mobile application through Xcode, Android Studio, and Browser.
- Understand and learn the code of existing web applications to translate it into a new application with API services.
- Designed and maintained CMS website for the client.
- Writing SQL queries for fixing user errors on Relational databases.
- Collaborate for scrum meetings with the teams and supervisor.
- Designed and implemented a desktop-first approach to web applications.
- Meeting and Presenting the finished web app to the client.
- Developed eCommerce mobile app as a single-page application.

Tech Stacks: PHP, Javascript, C#, ASP.NET, Ionic, Angular, MySQL

Full-stack Developer

FREELANCE

March 2019 - July 2019 (5 mons)

- Developed merchant admin website for a marketplace both back-end and front-end.
- Developed a website and mobile application for a blood donation system.
- Developed a mobile application for a patient information system. Collaborate with the teams to meet client needs and goals.

Tech Stacks: C#, PHP, ASP.NET, React Native, Ionic, Angular, Laravel, MSSQL, MySQL

Web Developer Intern

JENUS WEB SOLUTIONS INC

Dec 2018 - March 2019 (4 mons)

- Created designs for website mockups, look books, and logos.
- Maintained and Optimized existing CMS website.
- Cooperated with a web designer and web developer.
- Fixed bugs and implemented enhancements on the website. Developed web application using web framework.

Tech Stacks: Laravel, Vue.js, WordPress

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

STI COLLEGE NOVALICHES

June 2015 - May 2019

PROGRAMMING / MARKUP / SCRIPTING LANGUAGES

HTML SASS **JSON** CSS SQL Javascript PHP C# Typescript

WEB FRAMEWORKS / LIBRARIES / DATABASE / TOOLS

Jquery Bootstrap Laravel Vue.js Angular 2+ React.js ASP.NET MVC/Core Tailwind CSS Ionic Framework **RXJS** Git **AWS** Node.js React Native Redux Express.js MongoDB MySQL **MSSQL** Capacitor Cordova Jira Next.js **Firebase**

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Website Optimization Critical Thinking Website development Adaptability Teamwork Agile Framework Responsive Web Design **Problem Solving** Time Management Android and IOS App Development Interpersonal communication skills SQL and database concepts

LANGUAGE

Filipino (Native) **English** (Professional)